### CONTACT

Bangkok, Thailand 064-451-9941 viranda.soonthornpakdee@gmail.com www.viranda.me

## MY PROFILE

My name is Viranda and you can call me Dao, 29 years old. Over 8 years of experience in the Digital Industry. I've been doing many roles starting from UX/UI Designer and got promote to Product Owner. I able to effectively coordinate tasks to accomplish projects with timeliness and creativity. My greatest strength is solid organisational skills including attention to detail and multi-tasking skills, Strong aptitude and desire to learn new technologies and tools.



## **SKILLS**

- Project Management
- Project Planing
- Agile Methodologies
- Design Thinking
- User Interface Design
- User Experience (UX)
- Design System / Design Token

# **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Sketch
- CSS
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustration
- Jira
- Click Up

### INTERESTS

- Design Trends
- HTML/CSS
- New Technologies Tools
- English Practice

## **EXPERIENCES**

May 2023 - Present

#### Product Owner | Innovation Product Design & UX/UI Manager (Invitrace CO., LTD)

Group 5 Virtual Hospital Consultant

- Find current problem and requirement And design new features to support virtual hospital business.

Thonburi Hospital Group Digital Transformation

- Patient centric transformation with 3P concept (People, Process, Platform)
- UX Reseach & Strategic Transformation plan
- Digital Strategic Health Transformation plan & Solutions Team Building
- Lean Process -Performance Control -Task and Timeline Management -Product Roadmap

July 2021 - Oct 2021

#### LEAD UX/UI DESIGNER (THE LIVINGOS CO., LTD)

- Researching, User interview, Develop user interface design and Design system
- Collaborate with Product owner, Business Unit and Developers to crafts consistent user experiences and sensible user interfaces that accommodate both. Be person in charge in squad ERP and Service Maintenance.
- Team planing, Performance Controller, Team Building, Workshop, Tasks and Timeline management

July 2021 - Oct 2021

### **UX MANAGER (AYUDHYA CAPITAL AUTO LEASE PUBLIC CO., LTD)**

Research and Created user workflow, screen flow and wireframe. Collaborated with UI designer to develop a design system. Collaborated with Product Owner and Product Manager to set up the delivery team's working process and Agile practice Person in charge in squad platform and Insurance

July 2021- June 2022

#### ASSISTANT UX/UI MANAGER (BUZZEBEES CO.,LTD.)

Manage team's work, timeline and working process. Building the very first design systems, loyalty program development. Work and communicate with multiple teams to establish frameworks and maintain design quality. Keep track of ongoing / taken experiments while deliver learnings over quarters with team. As well as collaborating with team and researchers to create scalable and user-friendly product. Create end to end of Projects and Internal Products

# CERTIFICATES

Design Thinking

Thammasart University

- Foundation of User Experience Design
  Coursera By Google
- UX Design: 2 Analyzing User Data LinkedIn Learning Certificate
- Service Design Innovation
  Chulalongkorn University

## **EXPERIENCES**

Feb 2020 - July 2021

#### SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER (BUZZEBEES CO.,LTD.)

Ability in Design Thinking methodology full loop (User Research, Define a problem, Ideation, Wireframe, Prototype, and Testing) And collaborator with vendors to control performance and usability in the UI UX part. Design on web base in LINE Platform

June 2018 - Jan 2020

### PROJECT MANAGER / PRODUCT OWNER (BANGKOKSOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As a project Manager with designing background. I used to handle many types of tasks such as web design, application design and software design & development. I able to effectively coordinate tasks to accomplish projects with timeliness and creativity. My greatest strength is solid organisational skills including attention to detail and multitasking skills.

June 2016 - Jan 2020

#### SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER (BANGKOKSOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As an UX/UI Designer with an eye for great user interface design and have a passion for pixel-perfect precision. I'm working closely to developer to understand the depth of business and to make sure the scope and the direction of the product is aligned and within schedule. I have a little knowledge of HTML and CSS. so I can help reduce the developer's work and I can understand the database tables meanings and relationships.

## **EDUCATIONS**

2021 - 2015

#### BACHELOR DEGREE OF FINE AND APPLIED ART

Burapha University

2009 - 2012

#### **ENGLISH - JAPANESE LANGUAGE AND LITERATURE**

Satrinonthaburi School